Guide to the Prince William County Historic Newspapers Collection, 1851-1992
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center
Prince William County Historic Newspapers Collection
1851-1992
C301
George Mason University. Libraries. Special Collections Research Center.
9.0 boxes
Prince William County newspapers dating from 1851 to 1992.
Prince William County Library.
Access Restrictions
There are no access restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by the Prince William County Library in November 2016.
Historical Note
The "Manassas Journal" began under W.H.W. Moran & Co. in 1895. In 1945, the "Manassas Messenger" was created, and on November 22, 1951, the "Manassas Journal" and the "Manassas Messenger" merged to from the "Journal Messenger." The "Journal Messenger" existed until 1997 and leaned Democratic. The "Prince William News," published under Clarence W. Wagener, was a weekly paper from 1921 to 1923. "Potomac News" began in 1959 in Dumfries, VA and in 1979 moved to Woodbridge, VA until it ended in 2008.
The miscellaneous series contains a few issues from newspapers like the "Richmond News Leader" (circa 1896-1992), "Richmond Times-Dispatch" (circa 1903-1992), the "Fauquier Democrat" (1905-1989), and the "Alexandria Gazette" (1834-1974) among others. The "Richmond News Leader" and "Richmond Times-Dispatch" became the two main papers in Richmond in the early 20th century.
Scope and Content
Several newspapers from Prince William County and other Virginia papers such as the "Manassas Journal," "Manassas Messenger," "Potomac News," the "Prince William News," and the "Journal Messenger." SCRC also has a few issues from the "Alexandria Gazette," the "Richmond News Leader," "Richmond Times-Dispatch" and news clippings. The papers in this collection date roughly from 1861 to 1992.
Arrangement
Series 1: The Manassas Journal, 1904-1951 (Oversize Box 1)
Series 2: The Prince William News, 1921-1923 (Oversize Box 2)
Series 3: The Manassas Messenger, 1945-1951 (Oversize Box 3)
Series 4: The Journal Messenger, 1951-1986 (Oversize Boxes 4-7)
Series 5: Potomac News, 1972-1988 (Oversize Box 8)
Series 6: Miscellaneous, 1851-1992 (Oversize Box 9)
Related Material
Special Collections Research Center has collections related to Prince William and other newspaper collections such as the and.
Index Terms
Subjects:
Alexandria County (Va.)--Newspapers.; Fauquier County (Va.)--Newspapers.; Local history.; Manassas (Va.)--Newspapers.; Prince William County (Va.)--Newspapers.
Document Types:
Newspapers.
Contents List
- Series 1: The Manassas Journal, 1904-1951 (Oversize 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 8, 1904 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 26, 1906 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 8, 1906 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 15, 1910 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 16, 1910 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 24, 1910 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 4, 1935 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 18, 1918 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 16, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, February 6, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, March 26, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, April 2, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, May 7, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 4, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 9, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, August 13, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, August 20, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 3, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 24, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, October 1, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, November 5, 1920 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 21, 1921 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, February 4, 1921 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, April 22, 1921 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 10, 1921 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 24, 1921 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 8, 1921 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 15, 1921 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, November 4, 1921 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 6, 1922 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 6/13, 1922 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, March 31, 1922 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, April 7, 1922 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, April 28, 1922 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 30, 1922 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 1, 1922 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 5, 1923 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 12, 1923 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 19, 1923 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 26, 1923 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, February 16, 1923 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, March 3, 1923 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, March 16, 1923 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, April 13, 1923 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, April 23/27, 1923 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, May 18, 1923 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, December 10, 1925 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 28, 1926 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, May 27, 1926 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 3, 1926 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, March 21, 1929 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 3, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, March 27, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, April 3, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, May 29, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 12, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 19, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 26, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 3, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 17, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 24, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, August 14, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, August 28, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 4, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 11, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 25, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, October 2, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, October 9, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, October 16, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, November 13, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, November 27, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, December 13, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, December 18, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 8, 1930 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, April 2, 1931 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, April 23, 1931 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, May 7, 1931 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, May 14, 1931 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 11, 1931 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 24, 1931 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, October 1, 1931 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, November 5, 1931 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, December 31, 1931 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 21, 1932 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 16, 1932 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 14, 1932 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, August 11, 1932 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 1, 1932 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 29, 1932 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, March 9, 1933 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, March 15, 1933 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, April 27, 1933 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 22, 1933 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, August 17, 1933 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 25, 1934 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, May 3, 1934 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, May 10, 1934 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, May 24, 1934 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, August 23, 1934 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, September 13, 1934 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, October 4, 1934 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, October 25, 1934 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, December 20, 1934 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, May 9, 1935 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, May 16, 1935 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 6, 1935 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 13, 1935 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 4, 1935 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, October 10, 1935 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, October 17, 1935 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, November 21, 1935 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, November 28, 1935 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 2, 1936 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, March 5, 1936 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 16, 1936 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 23, 1936 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, October 15, 1936 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, April 22, 1937 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, February 1, 1940 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, January 6, 1944 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, August 16, 1945 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, December 30, 1948 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 6, 1950 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, June 28, 1951 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, July 5, 1951 (Box 1)
  - The Manassas Journal, November 15, 1951 (Box 1)
- Series 2: The Prince William News, 1921-1923 (Oversize 2)
  - The Prince William News, April 21, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, April 28, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, May 5, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, May 12, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, May 19, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, May 21, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, May 26, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, June 2, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, June 9, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, June 30, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, July 7, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, July 14, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, July 21, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, July 28, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, August 11, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, August 18, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, August 25, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, September 1, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, September 8, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, September 15, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, September 22, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, September 29, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, October 6, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, October 13, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, October 20, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, October 27, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, November 3, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, November 10, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, November 17, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, November 24, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, December 1, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, December 8, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, December 15, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, December 22, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, December 29, 1921 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, January 5, 1922 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, January 12, 1922 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, January 19, 1922 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, January 26, 1922 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, February 2, 1922 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, February 9, 1922 (Box 2)
  - The Prince William News, January 11, 1923 (Box 2)
- Series 3: The Manassas Messenger, 1945-1951 (Oversize 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, June 15, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, June 22, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, June 29, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, July 6, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, July 13, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, July 20, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, July 27, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, August 3, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, August 10, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, August 17, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, August 24, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, August 31, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, September 7, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, September 14, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, September 21, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, September 28, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, October 5, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, October 12, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, October 19, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, October 26, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, November 2, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, November 9, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, November 16, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, November 23, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, November 30, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, December 7, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, December 14, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, December 21, 1945 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, January 4, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, January 11, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, January 18, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, January 25, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, February 1, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, February 8, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, February 15, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, February 22, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, March 1, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, March 8, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, March 15, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, March 22, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, April 5, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, April 12, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, April 19, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, April 26, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, May 3, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, May 10, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, May 17, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, May 24, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, May 31, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, June 7, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, June 14, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, June 21, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, June 28, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, July 5, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, July 12, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, July 19, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, July 26, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, August 2, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, August 9, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, August 16, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, August 23, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, August 30, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, September 6, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, September 13, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, September 20, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, September 27, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, October 4, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, October 11, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, October 18, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, October 25, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, November 1, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, November 8, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, November 15, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, November 22, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, November 29, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, December 6, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, December 13, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, December 20, 1946 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, September 19, 1947 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, October 31, 1947 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, April 20, 1948 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, May 6, 1949 (Box 3)
  - The Manassas Messenger, November 15, 1951 (Box 3)
- Series 4: The Journal Messenger, 1951-1986 (Oversize 4-7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 22, 1951 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 29, 1951 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, December 6, 1951 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, December 13, 1951 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, December 20, 1951 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 9, 1958 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, January 8, 1959 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, January 15, 1959 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, January 22, 1959 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, April 30, 1959 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 14, 1959 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 5, 1959 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 20, 1961 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 27, 1961 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 15, 1962 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, February 28, 1963 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, March 21, 1963 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, March 28, 1963 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, March 18, 1965 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 14, 1965 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 30, 1968 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 1, 1969 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger-100 Years of Service, May 8, 1969 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 15, 1969 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 22, 1969 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 29, 1969 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 28, 1971 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, February 4, 1972 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, June 23, 1972 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, June 26, 1972 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, February 21, 1973 (Box 4)
  - The Journal Messenger, April 30, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 4, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 11, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger-Centennial, May 11, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 16, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 18, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 21, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 23, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 25, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, June 11, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, June 13, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, June 15, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, June 18, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, June 20, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, June 25, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, June 29, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 2, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 9, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 13, 1973 (Box 5)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 16, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 18, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 20, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 23, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 25, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 30, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, August 1, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, August 13, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, August 15, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, August 17, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, August 20, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, August 22, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, August 24, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, August 27, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, August 31, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, September 7, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, September 28, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 1, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 3, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 8, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 15, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 17, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 19, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 24, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 26, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 29, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 30, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 31, 1973 (Box 6)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 1, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 2, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 5, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 6, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 7, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 8, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 9, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 13, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 14, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 15, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 16, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 19, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 20, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 21, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 22, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 23, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 26, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 27, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 28, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 29, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 30, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, December 3, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, December 4, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, December 6, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, December 7, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, December 19, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, December 20, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, December 28, 1973 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, February 6, 1974 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, February 13, 1974 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, February 15, 1974 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, February 18, 1974 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, August 9, 1974 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, February 15, 1975 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 29, 1975 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, May 13, 1976 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, February 21, 1979 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, February 22, 1979 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, November 29, 1979 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, December 28, 1983 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, October 22, 1984 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger-Neighbors, May 1985 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger-Neighbors, January 1986 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 17, 1986 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 19, 1986 (Box 7)
  - The Journal Messenger, July 21, 1986 (Box 7)
- Series 5: Potomac News, 1972-1988 (Oversize 8)
  - Potomac News, June 23, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, June 26, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, June 28, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, June 30, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, July 5, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, July 7, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, July 12, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, July 14, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, July 19, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, July 21, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, July 26, 1972 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, May 11, 1973 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 26, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 29, 1975 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, July 2, 1976 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, February 2, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, February 4, 1977 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, February 20, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, February 21, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, August 10, 1979 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, January 18, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, February 1, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, August 29, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 8, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 10, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 11, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 12, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 15, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 16, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 17, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 18, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 19, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 22, 1980 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 4, 1984 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, January 30, 1985 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, January 29, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, July 21, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, September 10, 1986 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, January 28, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, February 11, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, July 22, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, October 21, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, November 4, 1987 (Box 8)
  - Potomac News, March 16, 1988 (Box 8)
- Series 6: Miscellaneous, 1851-1992 (Oversize 9)
  - "Manassas Concert Affords Rare Treat of Great Music", undated (Box 9)